ILGWU. Research Department wages and hours files, 5780/148
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 101C, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  Public Hearings for Women's Outerwear, Needlework, and Miscellaneous Fabricated Textiles Products Industry in Puerto Rico. Hearings. Volume 1
- U.S. Wage and Hour Division Industry Committee Number 101B, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  Public Hearings for the Children's Dress and Related Product Industry. Exhibits, Report, Findings of Fact, Recommendations, and Wage Order. Volume 2
- U.S. Wage and Hour Division Industry Committee Number 101B, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- U.S. Wage and Hour Divisions Industry Committee Number 101A, 1970-1971 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  Public Hearings for the Corsets, Brassieres, and Allied Garments Industry in Puerto Rico. Exhibits 41-75. Volume 4
- U.S. Wage and Hour Divisions Industry Committee Number 101, 1969-1971 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  Public Hearing for the Corsets, Brassieres, and Allied Garments Industry in Puerto Rico. Exhibits 12-40. Volume 3
- U.S. Wage and Hour Division Industry Committee Number 101A, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  Public Hearing for the Corsets, Brassieres, and Allied Garments Industry in Puerto Rico. Exhibits 1-11, Report, Findings of Fact, Recommendations, and Wage Order. Volume 2
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 111A, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contract Division Special Industry Committee 111A, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  Public Hearings for Men's and Boys' Clothing and Related Products Industry in Puerto Rico. Economic Report, Pre-hearing Statement of ILGWU, Report, Findings of Fact, and Recommendations for the Industry. Volume 2
- U.S. Wage and Hour Division Industry Committee Number 113A, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  Public Hearings for the Corsets, Brassieres, and Allied Garments Industry in Puerto Rico. Exhibits, Report, Findings of Fact, Recommendations, and Wage Order. Volume 2
- U.S. Wage and Hour Division Industry Committee Number 113A, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  Public Hearings for the Corsets, Brassieres, and Allied Garments Industry in Puerto Rico. Hearings. Volume 1
- U.S. Wage and Hour Division Industry Committee Number 113B, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  Public Hearings for the Children's Dress and Related Products Industry in Puerto Rico. Hearings. Volume 1
- U.S. Wage and Hour Division Industry Committee Number 113A, 1970-1972 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  Public Hearings for the Corsets, Brassieres, and Allied Garments Industry in Puerto Rico. Exhibit 7 Part 2. Volume 4
- U.S. Wage and Hour Division Industry Committee Number 113D, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- U.S. Wage and Hour Division Industry Committee Number 113C, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  Public Hearing for the Women's Outerwear, Needlework, and Miscellaneous Fabricated Textile Products Industry in Puerto Rico. Hearings. Volume 1
- U.S. Wage and Hour Division Industry Committee Number 113D, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  Public Hearing for the Women's and Children's Underwear and Women's Clouse Industry in Puerto Rico. Exhibits, Report, Findings of Fact, Recommendations, and Wage Order. Volume 2
- U.S. Wage and Hour Division Industry Committee Number 113E, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- U.S. Wage and Hour Division Industry Committee Number 113E, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- U.S. Wage and Hour Division Industry Committee Number 127B, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  Public Hearing for Hosiery Industry in Puerto Rico. Hearing, Economic Report, Supplement to Economic Report, and Wage Order.
- U.S. Wage and Hour Division Industry Committee Number 127A, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  Public Hearing for Men's and Boys' Clothing and Related Products Industry in Puerto Rico. Hearing, Economic Report, Supplement to the Economic Report, Wage Order.
- U.S. Wage and Hour Division Industry Committee Number 127D, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  Public Hearing for the Gloves and Mittens Industry in Puerto Rico. Hearing, Economic Report, Supplement to the Economic Report, and Wage Order
- U.S. Wage and Hour Division Industry Committee Number 128A, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  Public Hearing for the Women's and Children's underwear and Women's Blouse Industry in Puerto Rico. Exhibits, Report, Findings of Fact, Recommendations, Dissent, and Wage Order. Volume 2
- U.S. Wage and Hour Division Industry Committee Number 127C, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  Public Hearing for Leather, Leather Goods, and Related Products Industry in Puerto Rico. Hearing, Economic Report, Supplement to the Economic Report, and Wage Order.
- U.S. Wage and Hour Division Industry Committee Number 128A, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 15)
- U.S. Wage and Hour Division Industry Committee Number 128D, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  Public Hearing for the Children's Dress and Related Products Industry in Puerto Rico. Hearing. Volume 1